headstart.in 2019-06-26

# Privacy policy | Headstart Network

SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you register with us, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. We never sell it. 

Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about our new initiatives, entrepreneurship resources and other updates.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT

**How do you get my consent?**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a contributory pass order, verify your credit card, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at [admin@headstart.in](mailto:admin@headstart.in) or mailing us at Headstart Network Foundation, 3rd Floor, Above Icici, 1101, 24th Main Rd, Vysya Bank Colony, Jeewan Sathi Colony, 1st Phase, J P Nagar, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560078

SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 4 - PAYMENT

We use Razorpay for processing payments. We/Razorpay do not store your card data on their servers. The data is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) when processing payment. Your purchase transaction data is only used as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is not saved.

Our payment gateway adheres to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by us and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read terms and conditions of razorpay on [https://razorpay.com](https://razorpay.com/)

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your contribution related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a contribution that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

**Links**

When you click on links on our site, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

SECTION 7 - COOKIES

We use cookies to maintain session of your user. It is not used to personally identify you on other websites.

SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

?QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information to contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [admin@headstart.in](mailto:admin@headstart.in) or by mail at Headstart Network Foundation, 3rd Floor, Above Icici, 1101, 24th Main Rd, Vysya Bank Colony, Jeewan Sathi Colony, 1st Phase, J P Nagar, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560078
